Starting...
SMS: hi friend
Email: Will you make your appointment?
SMS: What's going on?
Email: Let's be friends
Email: What are you doing?
SMS: Welcome to the business
Email: I can't believe you've done this.
SMS: I'll pay you to be my friend
===============================
Starting...
SMS: this song slaps hard
Email: What do you think of this song?
SMS: yooo hoooo
Email: I hate this band
Email: Can you believe this song?
SMS: i'm a big fan
===============================
